Preliminary Inventory to the Carla A. Hills Papers, 1964-1993
Hoover Institution Archives
- F. ABA Annual/Post Annual Meetings; Hawaii, 7/31-8/6/80
  - 1. ABA Post-Annual Meeting Mauna Kea Beach Hotel, 8/5-9/80
  - 2. ABA- Annual Meeting; Honolulu, Hawaii, 1980 7/31-8/6/80
  - 3. ABA Annual Committee Reports
  - 4. ABA Section of Antitrust Law 1980 Annual & Post-Annual Mtg. Council Agenda; - Honolulu, HI; Kanuela, HI. (Binder), August 2, 1980 August 6-7, 1980
- A. ABA Antitrust Law Section General Correspondence (Box 151-152)
  - 1. ABA antitrust Law Section Vol. #4; General Correspondence, January 1980 thru December 1979
  - 2. ABA Antitrust Law Section Vol. #3 General Correspondence, 12/79
  - 3. ABA Vol. #1 Antitrust Law Section (General)
  - 4. ABA Vol. #2 Antitrust Law Section (General)
- B. ABA - Publications Committee Vol #2, July 1979 thru July 1980
- C. ABA - Publications Committee Vol. #1
- D. ABA - Publications Committee Miscellaneous Manuscripts
  - 1. ABA Antitrust Consent Decree Manual
  - 2. Antitrust Discovery Handbook (Notebook)
  - 3. Statistical Analysis of Private Antitrust Litigation Final Report (Notebook)
  - 4. Analysis of ABA Press; American Bar Association; April, 1978 (Notebook)
  - 5. American Bar Association; Section of Antitrust Law HANDBOOK; Preliminary Copy (Notebook)
- A. ABA Publications Committee Monographs Manuscripts (Box 153-154)
  - 1. The History of Merger Standards (notebook)
  - 2. U.S. Antitrust Law in International Patent and KNOW-HOW LICENSING (notebook)
  - 3. THE ROBINSON-PATMAN ACT POLICY and LAW (Volume I) (notebook), January, 1980
  - 4. THE ROBINSON-PATMAN ACT: POLICY and LAW (Volume I) (notebook), December, 1979
- B. ABA Publications Committee Monographs Manuscripts (Box 153-154)
  - 1. The FTC as an ANTIRUST ENFORCEMENT AGENCY -- ITS STRUCTURE, POWERS AND PROCEDURES, (notebook)
  - 2. SECTRIONS OF THE FTC ACT -- ITS ROLE IN ANTITRUST, (notebook)
- American Committee on East-West Accord
  - 1. American Committee on East-West Accord #2, General -- thru, June, 1979
  - 2. American Committee on East-West Accord Claremont Graduate School Program in International Relations
- D. American Council for Capital Formation Publications
- E. Anderson, Estates Grove C.
- F. Announcements (Miscellaneous), June, 1980 thru January, 1981
- G. Announcements (Miscellaneous), January, 1980 thru May 1980
- H. Announcements (Miscellaneous), July, 1979 thru December, 1979
- A. Brookings Institution (Box 155-156)
  - 1. Brookings Institution--Meeting, October 29-30, 1979
  - 2. Brookings Institution--Meeting, May 3-4, 1979
  - 3. Brookings Institution--Meeting, October 16-17, 1978
  - 4. Brookings Institution--Meeting, May 8-9, 1978
  - 5. Brookings Institution--Meeting, November 10-11, 1977
  - 6. Brookings Institution--Meeting, May 5-6, 1977
  - 7. Brookings Institution--Finance Committee
- B. Brown Griffin A/C Bill
- C. California Citizens' Commission on Reform "Fighting the Liability Balance"
- D. CARBINO, PERRY, HOHEMSE, Borough of Wyoning, et. al. USDC, Middle D. Pa. #77-938
- E. CAH--Cabiner Chair
- F. Carnegie Commission on the Future of Public Broadcasting
  - 1. Carnegie Commission Correspondence thru Vo. #2, 1/19/78
  - 2. Carnegie Commission--Billings
  - 3. Carnegie Commission--Roster
  - 4. Carnegie Commissions--Meeting Dates
- G. Carter Transition: Shaping Housing Development Policies by Charles L. Edson
- H. Catalyst, 3/18/80
- I. Catalyst, 3/6/79
- A. Cello
- B. Cello
- C. Address Changes for BK
- D. Christmas List (binder), January 1979
- E. Christmas Photo, 1979
- F. CHRON (CAH), November 1980
- G. CHRON (CAH), October, 1980
- H. CHRON (CAH), September, 1980
- I. CHRON (CAH), August 1980
- J. CHRON (CAH), July, 1980
- K. CITIES/PEOPLE IN DISTRESS--Draft National Urban Policy Discussion November, 1977
- L. CITIZENS UNION Distinguished Service Award Dinner honoring Walter E. Hanson, 4/17/79
- M. CIVIL SERVICE REFORM
- N. COMMITTEE FOR A NATIONAL MUSEUM OF THE BUILDING ARTS
- O. COMMITTEE FOR ECONOMIC DEVELOPMENT
- P. CONFERENCE BOARD "Corporate Programming/Planning Workshop AM-1, 5/6/80
- A. Dinner Parties, 1977-1978 (Box 159-161)
- B. DeLUCIA, Francis C. (HUD Employee) Adverse Action Appeal Hrg., 12/11/79
- C. DOLBEARE, Cushing N.
  - 1. DOLBEARE, Cushing N. Vol. #2 thru, 1/1/78
  - 2. DOLBEARE, Cushing N. Vol. #1 thru, 12/31/77
- D. ELI LILLY AND COMPANY
  - 1. Eli Lilly and Company Correspondence
- E. Financial Accounting Standards Advisory Council Meeting, 10/23/79
- F. Financial Accounting Standards Advisory Council, 7/18/79
- G. Financial Accounting Standards Advisory Council, 4/17/79
- H. Financial Accounting Standards Advisory Council
  - 1. FASAC Public Forum Committee
  - 2. FASAC Correspondence #9, October 1980 thru
  - 3. FASAC--Tosters
  - 4. FASAC--Meeting Dates
  - 5. FASAC--Special Process Committee
  - 6. Financial Accounting Standards Board Minutes
  - 7. FASAC--Minutes
  - 8. FASAC--Meeting, 7/16/80
  - 9. FASAC--Meeting, 4/15/80
  - 10. FASAC--Meeting, 1/14/80
  - 11. FASAC--Meeting, 10/28/80
- A. FASAC (Box 162-163)
  - 1. FASB--Oil/Gas Producers Materials from Rob Odle
- B. FASAC Exposure Drafts
  - 1. FASAC Exposure Drafts
- C. FASAC--Reports
- D. FASAC--Interpretation Statements
- E. FASAC Correspondences, May, 1980thru September, 1980
- F. FASAC Correspondence #7, January 1980 thru April 1980
- G. FASAC Correspondence #6, August 1979 thru December 1979
- A. Leafue of Women Voters; Presidential Debates (Box 164-165)
  - 1. L of WV - Presidential Debates; Correspondence, Oct. 1980
  - 2. L of WV - Presidential Debates; Correspondence, Nov. 1979
  - 3. L of WV - Presidential Debates; Misc./ Press Clippings
  - 4. L of WV - Presidential Debates; Notes
- B. Nareit 8th Annual Accounting /Tax Conference, Hotel Del Coronado San Diego, CA May 23-25, 1979
- C. National Cathedral School, Commencement Addfess, June 3, 1979
- D. Personal - Medical Bills
  - 1. Blue Cross/Blue Shield (Health Insurance)
  - 2. Medical Bills - Peabody Coal Form
  - 3. Medical (Latham & Watkins) 1979
- E. Receipts, 1977, 1978, 1979
- F. Personal/Miscellaneous (CAH) Vol #6, 1979 May thru July
- G. Personal/Miscellaneous (CAH) Vol. #7, 1979 August thru December
- H. Personal/Miscellaneous (CAH) Vol. #10, 1980 June thru September
- I. Personal/Miscellaneous (CAH) Vol #9, 1980 April thru May
- J. Personal/Miscellaneous (CAH) Vol. #8, 1980 January thru March
- A. Leafue of Women Voters; Presidential Debates (Box 164-165)
  - 1. L of WV - Presidential Debates; Correspondence Oct. 1980
  - 2. L of WV - Presidential Debates; Correspondence Nov. 1979
  - 3. L of WV - Presidential Debates; Misc./ Press Clippings
  - 4. L of WV - Presidential Debates; Notes
- B. Nareit 8th Annual Accounting /Tax Conference, Hotel Del Coronado San Diego, CA May 23-25, 1979
- C. National Cathedral School, Commencement Addfess, June 3, 1979
- D. Personal - Medical Bills
  - 1. Blue Cross/Blue Shield (Health Insurance)
  - 2. Medical Bills - Peabody Coal Form
  - 3. Medical (Latham & Watkins) 1979
- E. Receipts, 1977, 1978, 1979
- F. Personal/Miscellaneous (CAH) Vol #6, 1979 May thru July
- G. Personal/Miscellaneous (CAH) Vol. #7, 1979 August thru December
- H. Personal/Miscellaneous (CAH) Vol. #10, 1980 June thru September
- I. Personal/Miscellaneous (CAH) Vol #9, 1980 April thru May
- J. Personal/Miscellaneous (CAH) Vol. #8, 1980 January thru March
- A. Ropublican National Committee Council on Human Concerns (Box 166-168)
  - 1. RNC #5 Council On Human Concerns Subcom'tees Position Papers, 1/14/80
  - 2. RNC--Council on Human Concerns vol.#4, June 1979 thru August 1979
- B. Republican National Committee Douncil on Human Concerns
- C. RNC--Council on Human Concerns
  - 1. RNC--Council on Human Concerns Bibliographies
- D. Compain 80... Advocate Briefing Book (binder)
- A. The Carter Record (binder) (Box 168-169)
- B. Republican National [UNK] Council on Human Concerns
  - 1. RNC vol. #3 Council on Human Concerns, July 1978 thru May 1979
  - 2. RNC vol. #2 Council on Human Concerns
  - 3. RNC vol. #1 Council on Human Concerns
- C. St. Paul's Manor Caring Community Campaign, San Diego, CA, 6/7/80
- D. Senate Com'tee on the Judiciary Testimony, 3/20/80
- E. Signal--form 10-Q
- F. Signal--Highlights--, 1978
- G. Signal--Highlights--, 1979
- G. Signal--Highlights--, 1979
- H. Signal--Highlights--, 1980
- I. Signal Companies Inc. Vol. #1 Correspondence, 2/77 to 4/30/78
- J. Signal--Correspondence--Vol. #2, May 1978 to May 31, 1979
- A. Sloan Commission-- Final/Draft Rpts. (Box 170-171)
- B. Sloan Commission on Government & Higher Education
  - 1. S.C. on G. and H.E. (binder)
  - 2. S.C. on G. and H.E.- Meeting, 6/25-27/79
  - 3. Sloan Commission--Chicago, Illinois, 5/1-2/79
  - 4. Sloan Meeting, Phoenix, Arizona, 3/19-20/79
  - 5. Sloan Meeting February 5 & 6, Washington, D.C.
  - 6. Sloan Commission Meeting, 12/14/78
  - 7. Sloan--Meeting, 9/13/78
  - 8. Sloan Commission--Meeting Boston, Massachusetts, 6/26/78
  - 9. Sloan Commission--Meeting Washington, D.C., 5/1/78
- C. Sloan Commission
  - 1. Sloan Commission--Meeting La Jolla, CA, 3/13/78
  - 2. Sloan Commission--Meeting Washington, D.C., 1/23/78
  - 3. Sloan Commission-- Meeting Washington, D.C., 11/28/78
- A. Reagan Housing Policy Task Force (Box 172-173)
- B. NAHB Blueprint for Victory
- C. GSA - Reports to Congress
- A. Stanford Law School; Board of Visitors (Box 174-175)
  - 1. Stanford Board of Visitors; Billing
  - 2. Stanford Board of Visitors; Rosters
  - 3. Stanford Board of Visitors; 20th Annual Meeting, April 23-28, 1978
- B. Swearing - In HUD Nomination Hearings Before the BANKING, HOUSING & URBAN AFFAIRS Cmttee. U.S. Senate, 3/10/75 2/24 & 2/27/75
- A. Statements-- Vol. #4, May 1980 thru August 1980 (Box 175)
- B. Statements-- Vol. #3, January 1980 thru April 1980
- C. Statements-- Vol. #2, April 1979 thru December 1979
- D. Stevens Tennis Party, 5/18/80
- E. Times/Ford Foundation Conference on Media/Business Biltmore Hotel, Santa Varvara, CA, 2/8-10/80
- F. Trilateral Commission Vol. #2, December 1979 thru
- G. Trilateral Commission thru, November 1979
- H. Trojan [UNK] of Orange County "Communication Fair", 3/13/79
- I. United Way Annual Meeting, Oakland, California, 6/26/79
- J. University of Southern California Board of Trustees Meetings (binder)
- A. Chron--CAH --, June 1980-April 1978 (Box 176)
- B. Timesheets, November 1980-Feb.1979
- A. Cost of Government Regulation Study for the Business Roundtable Vols. #1-3 (Box 177-178)
- B. Draft Speech Materials Cabinet Members' Speeches Womens' Speeches
- C. Speech Materials (newsclips and letters)
- A. CAH Mail Log (Box 178-179)
- B. Cost of Government Regulations Study for the Business Roundtable Vols. #1-3
- A. Becker Securities Corporation (binde (Box 179-180)
- B. Carnegie Commission; Tarrytown, N.Y., July 18-20, 1978
- C. Carnegie Commission on the Future of Public Broadcasting
- Radio Factbook
  - D. Carnegie Commission on the Future of Public Broadcasting
- Television Factbook
  - E. Carnegie----Tarrytown Ken Mason Staff Paper on "Meanings of Word Public/Mission of Public Broadcasting", 7/18-20/78
  - G. Carnegie----Meeting Dallas, Texas, 6/25-26/78
- A. Carnegie - Meeting; Boston, Massachu, 5/19-20/78 (Box 181-182)
- B. Carnegie - Meeting; Lincoln, Nebraska, 4/20-21/78
- C. Carnegie - Meeting; Columbia, South Carolina, 3/16-17/78
- D. Carnegie Commission on the Future of Public Broadcasting
- A. Carnegie Commission (Box 183-184)
- B. Housing Authority of LA Corr.
- C. Pepperdine University Corr.
- A. Administrative Committee [UNK] [UNK] State Bar [UNK] District [UNK] (Box 185)
- B. Anderson, Thelbert [UNK]
- C. Claremont University Advisory Council
- D. Executive Committee of the Law in Free Sociery Project
- E. Lawyers Committee for the Re-Election of the President LA County, 1972
- F. Standing Committee on Discipline USDC Central District of, CA 1972-4
- G. University of Siuthern California Board of [UNK]
- H. University of Southern California Board of Councilors
- I. Week-at-a-Glance, 1964-1972
- A. National Editorial/Commintary Digest RNC Communications Civision (Box 186-187)
- B. Presidential Documents
- C. President's Press Conference 1. #9, February 26, 1975
- D. Republican Convention Platform
- E. President's Committee Federal Urban Program Summaries
- F. Republican Convention General
- G. Republican Convention
- A. State of the Union Message, (1977) (Box 188-190)
- B. Budget/State of the Union Editorials
- C. State of the Union Message
- D. RNC -- Subcommittee Reports
  - 1. RNC Jobs (Kolberg) (Lugar)
  - 2. RNC Health (Scott) Cavanaugh)
  - 3. RNC Housing (Kearney) (Newman)
  - 4. RNC Welfare Reform (Nathan)
  - 5. RNC Neighborhoods (Butter) (Wilson)
- E. White House Editorials/Comments on Recent News and News Summary
- F. White House News Conference, March 10 - 31, 1975
- G. White House News Conference, June, 1975
- H. White House News Conference, July, 1975
- I. White House News Conference, August, 1975
- Brookings Institution Pamphlets Meeting, 5/12-13/80 (Box 190-192)
  - Board Of Trustees Meeting, 10/29-30/80
  - Brookings Staff Research Briefing Book (Urban Capital Needs Study), 8/22/78
  - Bruce McLaury Remarks, 5/3/78
  - Bruce McLaury Address, 10/13/77
  - Financial Statements, 6/30/78
  - Financial Statements, 6/30/77 & 1976
  - Meeting Dates
  - Executive Committee Meeting, 1/12/81
  - Staff Newsletters
  - News Releases
  - Developement Reports -, 1981
  - Board of Trustees, 5/11-12/81
  - Executive Committee Meeting, 4/3/81
  - Executive Committee Meeting, 9/23/80
  - Executive Committee Meeting, 4/7/80
  - Executive Committee Meeting, [UNK]
  - Executive Committee Meeting, 6/29/81
  - Executive Committee Minutes (Binder)
- A. Economic Data vols 1-3) (Box 192-194)
- B. Monetary Policy Acts (binder), 1979
- C. State Finance Agencies in the Seventies Prepared for the Council of State Housing Agencies Fevruary 1981
- D. Housing Needs in the Eighties Prepared for the Council of State Housing Agencies
- E. The Gallagher Presidents' Report
- F. Legislative Manual, New York, 1975
- A. White House News Conference, September 1975 (Box 194-196)
- B. White House News Conference, October 1975
- C. White House News Conference, November 1975
- D. White House News Conference, March 1976
- E. White House News Conference, April 1976
- F. White House News and Comment, June 1975
- A. White House News and Comment, July 1975 (Box 197-199)
- B. White House News and Comment, August 1975
- C. White House News and Comment, January 1976
- A. White House News and Comment, February 1976 (Box 200-202)
- B. White House News and Comment, March 1976
- C. White House News and Comment, April 1976
- A. White House News and Comment, May 1976 (Box 203-205)
- B. White House News and Comment, June 1976
- C. White House News and Comment, July - August 1976
- A. White House News and Comment, July 1976 (Box 206-208)
- B. White House News and Comment, August 1-15, 1976
- C. White House News and Comment, August 16-31, 1976
- D. White House News and Comment, September 1-15, 1976
- A. White House News and Comment, October 1-15, 1976 (Box 209-211)
- B. Whtie House News and Comment, December 1976
- C. White House Press Releases
- D. Statistics Regarding Women
- A. White House News and Comment September 16-30, 1976 (Box 212-213)
- B. White House News and Comment October 16-31, 1976
- C. White House News and Comment November 1976
- A. Bills (CAH - RMH) (Box 214-215)
- B. Portrait (Duplicate)
- C. Portrait Artist Dinner, 2/13/78
- D. Professional Builder, 12/11/78
- E. R.N.C. "Tax Blitz", 9/20-22/78
- F. Republican State Central Committee of California, 12/9/77
- G. Ripon Society
- H. Senate Budget Committee Hearings, 3/15/78
- I. Slider, William T.
- J. Southern California Edison Company
- K. Stanford Business School Alumnae Biltmore Hotel, Los Angeles --, 2/8/78
- L. Seinger, Elinor Porter
- M. Trojan Guild, 2/17/77
- N. U.S.O. Woman of the Year Award Lunch Plaza Hotel, Grand Ballroom, 5/26/77
- O. U.S.C. Center for Public Affairs Board of [UNK]
- P. Washington Mortgage Co., Inc. Waikiki, Hawaii, 4/12/77
- Q. Washington University, 5/20/77
- R. Weyerheuser Company Seattle, Washington, 4/22/77
- S. Wickes Corporation San Diego, California, 1/11-12/78
- T. Women Lawyers' Association of L.A.
- U. World Business Council, 1/22-25/77
- V. Yale University Gordon Grand Fellow
- W. Young Presidents Organization Atlanta Georgie, [UNK]
- X. Zahedi Dinner Party, 9/28/78
- Y. American Association of School Administrators Las Vegas, Nevada, 2/26/77
- A. Armco Steel Corporation (Box 215-217)
- B. Aspen Institute for Humanistic Studies Hawaii, 11/5-18/78
- C. [UNK] of Junior [UNK], Inc., 5/1/77
- D. Automobile [UNK]
- E. Bechtel [UNK] [UNK] [UNK]
- F. [UNK] [UNK]
- G. Camp (1977) [UNK]
- H. Center for Law/Social Policy
- I. Christmas Photo/Card, (1978)
- J. Christmas Photos, (1977)
- K. Connecticut General Life Insurance Company
- L. Democratic Research Organization
- M. Distinguished American Award Honorary Committee, 9/20/78
- N. D.C. Court of Appeals Application
- O. Edison Electric Institute Annual Convention, Houstin, Tx., 4/12/78
- P. Financial Executives Institute Washington, D.C., 10/17/77
- Q. Harvard, 10/12-13/77
- R. Hawaii Executive Conference Waikiki and Mauna Kea, 4/1-8/78
- S. House Com'tee on Banking, Financial & Urban Affairs Minority Staff Luncheon/discussion, 7/14/78
- T. Hugh O'Brien Youth Foundation
- U. HUD Clip Sheets
- V. HUD Second Reunion, 2/14/78
- W. IBM Marketing Forum Palm Springs, Ca., 3/21/77
- X. Ice Skating
- Y. Invitations, 12/19/78-12/31/78
- Z. Invitations, 10/78-
- aa. Invitations, 6/78-9/78
- bb. Lake Forest College, 6/3/78
- cc. MGIC Board
- dd. Marilyn Ryan Fund - Raising [UNK] L.A., Ca. 10/5/77
- ee. Marlborough School/Associates Party L.A., Ca. 12/6/77
- ff. Maryland Tribute to Ferald R. Ford, 6/13/78
- gg. Mills College Convocation Oakland, Ca., 9/14/77
- hh. Moderates (Duplicate)
- ii. Nieghborhood: River City Guidlines for South Loop
- jj. Pacific Mutual Board of Directors
- A. Personal/Miscellaneous, 1974 (Box 217-219)
- B. Personal/Miscellaneous, 1973
- C. CAH Personal Disqualification in Certain Matters
- D. Personal/Miscellaneous (CAH) Department of Justice, 1974, 1975
- E. Personal/Miscellaneous, August thru December, 1976
- F. Personal/Miscellaneous, January thru July, 1976
- G. Personal/Miscellaneous, January, 1977
- A. ASE - Jack Anderson (Box 219-220)
- B. ASE - John G. Muers Report
- C. ASE - Progrmas Memoranda
- D. ASE - Monthly Newsletters
- E. ASE - Contribution Acknowledgements
- F. ASE - Press
- G. ASE - Purpose & Progrmas
- H. ASE - Schlesinger, James R. Testimony before the Joint Economic Committee, 5/25/77
- I. ASE - Reckefeller, Melson A. Statement before the Senate Finance Committee, 9/13/77
- J. ASE - Congtessional Correspondence
- K. ASE - Sant, Roger W.
- L. ASE - Louis Harris Poll, June 1977
- M. ASE - CBS News Bew York Times Poll Energy -- August, 1977
- N. ASE - Press Releases
- O. ASE - Notes
- P. ASE - Groups with Similar or Overlapping Interests
- Q. ASE - Senator Glenn Bill
- R. ASE - Summary Case Statement
- S. ASE - Articles of Incorporation
- T. ASE - By - Laws
- U. ASE - Legal Opinions
- V. ASE - Miscellaneous Reports: Publications & Articles
  - 1. Carter's Energy Message
  - 2. Energy Research Development Administration by Lee Schippor Towards More Productive Energy Use
  - 3. Forecast of Likely U.S. Energy Supply Demand Balances for 1985-2000 Implications for U.S. Energy Policy U.S. Commerce, 1977
  - 4. Miscellaneous Articles
  - 5. National Academy of Science; Energy Conservation - How the Policy Makers Affect the Consumers by Roger W. Sant
  - 6. National Leadership Conference on Energy Policy, 1977
  - 7. Republican Report
- W. ASE - Miscellaneous Reports: Publications & Articles
  - 1. American Institute of Architects
  - 2. Brochure
  - 3. Business Roundtable Energy Position Paper, 9/12/77
  - 4. Channel Home Centers
  - 5. Concern, Inc.
  - 6. CONCO - Speaker's Program
  - 7. Development Associates Confidential Report on Fundraising
  - 8. Donors
  - 9. International Conference on Energy Use Management, 10/24-28/77
  - 10. National Energy Outlook Executive Summary, 1976
  - 11. 101 Ways to Save Money by Saving Energy
  - 12. Perspective on Energy Policy bt Elliot L. Richardson and Frank G. Zarb --, 12/16/76
  - 13. Utility "Bill" Stuffer
  - 14. Winter, Elmer L. Suggested Thought Starters
  - 15. World Business Council Report to Members, 1976
  - 16. Worldwatch
- X. CAH Chron File (HUD), March, 1974 - June, 1977
- A. Housing Policies for the `70's Briefing Book Prepared for National Organization Officials (Box 221)
- B. Potomac Institute Study Synopsis of and Comments on
- C. Annual Housing Survey
- D. Housing Needs
- E. Housing DATA Briefing Paper
- F. Housing and Urban Affair Daily
- G. Homeownership Options
- H. Housing & Community Development Act of 1974
- I. Financial Institutions Act
  - 1. Statement of CAH on 5/15/75
  - 2. Report Committee on Banking Housing & Urban Affairs Accompanying S.1267 with Additional Views
  - 3. John C. Weicher 12/10/75 Statement Before House Subcomittee on Financial Institutions /Supervision Regulations /Insurance
  - 4. Explanation of Proposed Financial Institutions Act of 1976 House Committee on Banking Currency/Housing, 2/76
  - 5. John C. Weecher 2/25/76 Statement Before Task Force on Tax Expenditures of House Committee in the Budget
- J. American Express
- K. Blackstone, Inc.
- L. Magnin
- M. Insurance
- N. Jonathan Club
- O. Medical
- P. Personal/Tax Deductible
- Q. Saks Fifth Avenue
- R. United Airlines
- A. ABA - Section of Antitrust Law Midwinter Council Mtg -, January, 1981 (Box 222-223)
- B. ABA-Section of Antitrust Law Spring Meeting, April 1, 1981
- C. ABA Antitrust Section Fall Council Meeting, 11/4/81
- D. ABA Section of Antitrust Law 1981 Annual & Post Annual Meeting
- E. ABA Publications Committee
- D. ABA Meetings, 1981
- A. Chron Files -, 1974 (Box 223-224)
- B. CAH Telephone Records -, 1973
- C. Library Organization
- D. Stanford Annual Fund Drive
- E. CAH Duplicate Time Sheets -, 1971 and 1974
- F. Daily Telephone Reports -, 1971
- G. Personal/Miscellaneous -, 1971
- H. Los Angeles County Bar Indingent Defense -, 1966-1969
- I. Los Angeles County Bar Association Federal Courts and Practice Committee, 1969 - 1972
- J. State Bar Conference Committee Materials
- A. Taylor's Encyclopedia of Government Officials Federal & State (Box 224-226)
- B. Reexamination of Federal Housing & Community Development Policies & Programs Highlights of Paper, Dtd. June 1973
- C. Executive Summary of the 1976 Report on National Growth and Development, February 1976
- D. Seventh Annual Report on the National Housing Goal Subsidized Housing
- E. Note - Procedural Due Process in Government Subsidized Housing
- F. Transition - Memorandum to Carter Transition Team
- G. 1974 & 1975 Annual Report of the U.S. Dept. of Housing & Urban Development
- H. U.S. Railway Association Preliminary System Plan Vol. I-III
- I. The Urban Lawyer
- A. National Housing Goals (Box 226-228)
- B. National Housing Goals 7th Annual Report
- C. National Growth/Development Report
  - 1. National Growth/Development Report 2nd Biennal Report
  - 2. National Growth/Development Report 3rd Biennal Report: The Changing Issues for National Growth
  - 3. National Growth/Development Report Perspectives on National Growth/Development a Compact History, 1776 - 1976
  - 4. National Growth/Development Report U.S.; It's International Programs for Human Settlements
  - 5. National Growth/Development Report State Growth Management
  - 6. National Growth/Development Report Summary of Proceedings of 1976 Regional Seminars on Growth/Development
  - 7. Urban Growth Management Summary Evaluation Research
- D. The Neighborhood Succession Process, Executive Summary of a HUD Research Project Report
- E. New Communities: Problems/Potentials
- F. New York City Crisis